<pkmkdoc spec="1.12"><properties><title>Chime</title><build>/Users/matt/Desktop/Chime v0.5 - Mac OS X.pkg</build><organization>org.chime</organization><userSees ui="both"/><min-target os="3"/><domain system="true"/></properties><distribution><versions min-spec="1.000000"/><scripts></scripts></distribution><contents><choice title="Chime" id="choice0" description="The chime compiler front-end and runtime libraries needed for building standalone executables." starts_selected="true" starts_enabled="true" starts_hidden="false"><pkgref id="org.chime.chime.pkg"/><pkgref id="org.chime.libchime.pkg"/><pkgref id="org.chime.libchimeruntime.pkg"/><pkgref id="org.chime.chime-manpage.pkg"/></choice><choice title="Chime Compiler Library" id="choice1" description="Libraries and headers that can be used to programmatically parse chime source code." starts_selected="false" starts_enabled="true" starts_hidden="false"><pkgref id="org.chime.chime.libchimecompiler.pkg"/></choice></contents><resources bg-scale="none" bg-align="topleft"><locale lang="en"><resource mime-type="text/rtf" kind="embedded" type="license"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1138\cocoasubrtf230
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 LucidaGrande;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs26 \cf0 Copyright (c) 2011, Matthew Massicotte\
All rights reserved.\
\
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms without modification are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\
\
- Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\
- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\
- Redistributions of modified source and binaries are forbidden without the expressed written consent of the current Chime maintainer, Matthew Massicotte.\
\
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.}]]></resource><resource mime-type="text/rtf" kind="embedded" type="welcome"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1138\cocoasubrtf230
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 LucidaGrande;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs26 \cf0 Chime is a statically-compiled programming language with many dynamic features.  It features a class- and trait-based inheritance system, a very loose type system, closures and a built-in build automation mechanism.\
\
Please remember that this is a Technical Preview.  Chime 0.5 does not have a stable syntax, compiler, runtime, or core library.  Buyer beware.\
\
Included in this package:\
- The chime Compiler\
- The Chime Runtime Library\
- The Chime Core Library\
- Optionally, the Chime Compiler Library}]]></resource></locale></resources><flags/><item type="file">01chime.xml</item><item type="file">02libchime.xml</item><item type="file">03libchimeruntime.xml</item><item type="file">04libchimecompiler.xml</item><item type="file">05chime.xml</item><mod>properties.title</mod><mod>properties.anywhereDomain</mod><mod>properties.systemDomain</mod></pkmkdoc>